I'll try to make this short,
but don't judge just off the
title. I(29f) went out for
dinner with husband (28m) last
night - nothing fancy just a
chain sports bar - and it
being a Friday, the place was
packed. We sit, place our
order, and we're catching up
on the day everything is going
fine. When the waitress
brought out our appetizer, my
husband grabs about 4 decent
sized tortilla chips and
scoops an actual mountain of
spinach dip with them and
shoved the whole thing in his
mouth. And when I say shoved I
mean SHOVED his fingers in his
mouth with the food. By the
time I'd had 3 chips with some
dip the entire rest of the
appetizer was gone so I was
already irked and embarrassed
because of course people were
staring at us. I said as much
to him and when he said he
didn't see what he was doing
wrong, I told him "you're
acting like you've never seen
food before, it's
embarrassing." He didn't say
another word to me after that,
and has barely spoke to me
today either. I don't think
I'm the asshole for telling
him I was embarrassed by how
he was eating and annoyed that
most of the appetizer was
eaten by him, but I may have
taken it too far with the last
comment. For further context
no, this isn't the first time
this has happened. I've told
him multiple times it's
embarrassing when he does this
and asked him why so I can try
to help or at least understand
a bit better. It's only at
this specific chain and his
answer always is either idk or
that he "really loves the
spinach dip" they have. He
also does this at home but I
don't really care when he's at
home because I'm not going to
dictate how he acts in the
privacy of our house. Also to
note because I'm sure people
may ask, no he did not grow up
in a food insecure household,
they weren't rich but not
struggling that much. And
neither are we struggling now.
No there is no history with an
eating disorder either in him
or his family. Am I the
asshole?